[{"answer": " my friend called", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "He did", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "He did", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Nothing wrong with old age, my friend...long as you get there", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Where are you transmitting from", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Whatta ya know.  that place, born and raised", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh, I loved it.  I wish you'd gone", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You work too hard, my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "No wait, don't go", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "But you're not...you're not still here", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "C'mon, man.  Get inside.  I'll come over. We'll play some that place", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Go in where", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What?  What is it", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Whatta you mean she's not here", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "That'll never work.  They'll just think you're crazy", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No.  Nobody got...  Wait a minute.  I might not know who he is, but I know where he's gonna be.  I got the case file.  We know what he's gonna do before he does it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "They will if they catch him in the act. You can make that happen, Dad.  You can tail the victim and call it in at just the right moment", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I do know.  I'm a cop.  This is what I do", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah, it was a close call, but..", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Close is just close if you're still alive to talk about it, y'kno", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend, you still there", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You all right", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You remember my friend", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You know what I'm saying", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You know what I'm saying", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Well, I think you do", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Let me tell you what I know, my friend.  You went to Saint my friend with my friend.  You lived five blocks from her.  You liked her.  But she ain't interested.  That must've hurt, huh", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "So, what'd you do about it, my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You fight fires, honey", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I bet you do", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "He took your wallet", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "No.  This isn't what you think", "docId": "Frequency.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Okay, okay.  I need to go say something to my friend and finish up with the guy on the radio", "qsentId": 34}]